teachlr.com 2014-05-11

# Privacy policy - Teachlr

## Teachlr cares a lot about your privacy

### Personal information

We may collect personal information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register on the site, place orders, subscribe to newsletters, respond surveys, fill out forms, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. Users may be asked for, as necessary, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal information from users only if they voluntarily provide such information to us. Users can always refuse to provide personal information, although it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.

###  How we use your information

Any piece of information we collect from you may be used in any of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience: Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs

  * To improve our website: We continually work hard to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

  * To improve customer service (your information helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs in a more efficient way)

  * To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason, without your consent, other than for the sole purpose of delivering the purchased service requested..

  * To send periodic emails: The email address provided for order processing, will only be used to send you notifications, newsletters and updates.

### How Teachlr protects your information

We make use of a variety of security measures to guarantee the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

We use a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider's database, which will only be accessible to those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

### Cookies

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if its allowed by you) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information) 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile data about site traffic and site interaction so we can offer a better site experience. 

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

###  Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

###  Your Consent 

By using Teachlr.com, you consent to our website privacy policy.

###  Contact us 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please contact us by emailing info@teachlr.com

###  Address 

Teachlr Corp. 

San Francisco,

The Regent 12250

Panama.
